<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.tfx.sudoku</id>
  <name>Sudoku T</name>
  <version>1.06</version>
  <vendor email="15755502377@163.com" url="15755502377@163.com">tianfangxu</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[ 
  <div>
    Sudoku is a logic-based, combinatorial number-placement puzzle. The objective is to fill a  9 × 9 grid with digits so that each column, each row, and each of the nine   3 × 3  subgrids (known as "boxes" or "regions") contain all the digits from 1 to 9. The puzzle setter provides a partially completed grid, which has a unique solution.
  </div>
  <div>
    <b>1.Structure:</b>
    <div>
      The grid is divided into 81 cells, arranged in 9 rows and 9 columns. The 9 subgrids each have a 3 × 3  configuration.
    </div>
    <b>2.Rules:</b>
    <div>
      Each digit from 1 to 9 must appear exactly once in every row, column, and subgrid. No cell can contain a number that violates these conditions.
    </div>
  <div>
  <div>
    数独是一种基于逻辑的组合数字布局谜题。目标是用数字填充一个9×9的网格，使每一列、每一行和九个3×3子网格中的每一个都包含从1到9的所有数字。拼图设置器提供了一个部分完成的网格，它有一个独特的解决方案。
  </div>
  <div>
    <b>1.结构：</b>
    <div>
      网格分为81个单元格，排列成9行9列。9个子网格每个都有3×3的配置
    </div>
    <b>2.规则：</b>
    <div>
      从1到9的每个数字必须在每一行、每一列和每一个子网格中恰好出现一次。任何单元格都不能包含违反这些条件的数字
    </div>
  <div>
]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
      v1.00 Create a random Sudoku with moderate difficulty. And it can mark the answers you are unsure about.<br>
      v1.01 Fixed initialized number, non adjustable<br>
      v1.02 you can customize the mode operation<br>
      v1.03 Add a prompt after verifying the results, The way to adjust the prompt is not to directly prompt the correct answer, but to prompt based on the current operation data<br>
      v1.04 Initialize the answers already filled in by the user<br>
      v1.05 Highlight the currently selected number. And you can select the initialized number<br>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="201.0"/>

  <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/plugin_compatibility.html
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <!-- Add your extensions here -->
    <toolWindow id="Sudoku" factoryClass="com.tfx.MainUI"
                canCloseContents="false"
                anchor="right"/>
  <!--  data persistent  -->
    <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.tfx.MyPersistentStateComponent"/>
  </extensions>

  <actions>
    <!-- Add your actions here -->
    <action id="Sudoku" class="com.tfx.SudokuRun" text="Sudoku" description="Sudoku" >
      <add-to-group group-id="WindowMenu" anchor="last"/>
    </action>
  </actions>

</idea-plugin>